Alice: I think he’s Nadine’s hairdresser. He works inside, other people help him.
George: But he doesn’t work at weekends. Hairdressers work on Saturdays.
Alice: Not all hairdressers.
Charlie: He isn’t a chef, I’m sure. Pubs are full at weekends.
And James says he cooks British food, but his speciality is spaghetti carbonara. That’s Italian, not British!
I think he’s a hairdresser, too.
George: But Nadine says they’re friends, and then she says, ‘I don’t think he has children’.
She doesn’t know. I think that’s strange. I think he’s Tyler’s dentist.
He has special qualifications, and remember, ‘People don’t always like me’. Nobody likes dentists.
Alice: We need to agree.
Presenter: Your time’s up, Team B.
So what’s Mike’s job?
Alice: We think he’s a hairdresser.
Presenter: Mike, what do you do?
Mike: I’m Tyler’s dentist.
Presenter: Yes, Mike is Tyler’s dentist.
He says nobody likes dentists, but we like you, Mike!
Thank you very much indeed.